

Ferencz Balog

Junior Web Developer

Passion, Challenge-seeker, Professional improvement, are those three expressions that describe me.

In 2016 I accepted a job at a theater because of the passion of backstage activities and achieving new skills. Three years later I accepted the challenge to run a small enterprise alone from the passion of cycling and a few months later I started to improve my abilities as Sound Engineer and Web Developer.

Professional Skills

Advanced	Intermediate	Beginner	Still Learning
HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, WordPress, JSON	JavaScript, API fetch, Relational Databases	NodeJs, ReactJs	Java

balogferencz.artist@gmail.com

+40 752 813 860

github: FerenczBalog Linkedin: ferenczbalog

Spoken languages (CEFR scale)

C2: Hungarian, Romanian

C1: English

Work Experience

PUCK Puppet Theatre, Cluj-Napoca, 01.2017 - present Stage Technician

Earned soft skills:

Working under Pressure, Time Management, Attention to details, Communication, Engagement, Teamwork, Problem Solving

Balog I. Ferencz PFA, Cluj-Napoca, 07.2019 - present Founder, Food-Delivery, Stage Technician

Earned soft skills: Time Management, Attention to details, Communication

Passions

Cycling
Photography
Reading
Programming
Free-writing

Education

PLATFORMAIT.ro, 08.2020 - 08.2022

Hard skills:

Basics of HTML, CSS and JavaScript

TEACHBIT.ro, 08.2022 - present

Hard skills:

Advanced of HTML, CSS and JavaScript

My Projects

Mylifedash, 01.2023 - present

Hard skills: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, API fetch

Because we live in a fast-paced world, I am working on a webpage that can help everyone manage their life. The first version of the website contains only a weather function, providing a three-day forecast fetching

RiderBox, 03.2023 - present

Hard skills:

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JavaScript modules, OOP, JSON

While working in the theater as stage technician I missed a platform that can store the riders of current performances, so I created one. The first version was made using only HTML and CSS, the actual version is based on Javascript modules and Bootstrap.

The first web-portfolio, 2021

Hard skills: HTML, CSS

My first web portfolio was created with HTML and CSS, using layout technologies like flexbox and grid. The portfolio is a single page website organized in sections, writing about my passions, web development projects and about me. The webpage has an outer page, called blog, where I add

additional information about my projects.